你们好
Hey, you guys?
你们明天晚上有事吗
What are you doing tomorrow night?
嗯  让我看看  我想我…
Oh, well, let me see. l believe l'm....
是的  会在电视机前面睡着
Yes, falling asleep in front of the TV.
我经纪人给我六张票
Well, my agent hooked me up
去看一出很棒的舞台剧
with six tickets to a great play.
我也可以在那出舞台剧演出时睡着
l could fall asleep at a play.
是什么样的舞台剧
What is it?
是一个女人的独角戏叫做…
lt's a one-woman play called:
《你为什么不喜欢我》
Why Don't You Like Me?
副标题《一个悲惨女人的生命历程》
A Bitter Woman's Journey Through Life.
听起来挺有趣的
That sounds interesting.
是听起来挺有趣的
That does sound interesting.
听一个女人抱怨两个小时
To listen to a woman complain for two hours.
不会再…
l don't think it gets bet--
我懂你意思  我们可以开车
l know! l know. We can drive.
可以投票  可以工作
We can vote. We can work.
这些娘们还想要什么呢
What more do these broads want?
你们会喜欢的
Well, you guys will have a great time.
我保证
l promise.
什么  为什么你不去呢
What? How come you don't have to go?
我希望我可以  但是我发现…
l wish l could, but l found out...
我隔天要很早就起来工作
...that l have to be at work really early the next day,
所以我不能去
so l can't go.
但是你们可以用剩下的那张票
But take the extra ticket
邀请任何人去都可以
and invite whoever you want.
让我瞧瞧我最恨谁呢
Let's see. Who do l hate?
对不起
Oh, sorry.
哦  对不起
Oops, sorry.
好的
Okay.
好的  抬起来
Okay. Up we go.
天啊  好的
Oh, gosh, okay!
我可以问你一个问题吗
Can l ask you a question?
你觉得有没有可能
Do you think it's possible
两个朋友瞎搞
for two friends to fool around...
还觉得也没什么大不了的
...and not have it be a big deal?
不可能  为什么
No, l don't think that ever works. Why?
没事
No reason.
等一等  瑞秋
No, no. Rachel?
你想要跟谁瞎搞
Who do you want to fool around with?
没有人  别想太多
Nobody! Forget it.
乔伊吗
Joey?
或许吧
Maybe.
不行
You can't.
为什么
Why?
因为
Because!
说真的
Okay, seriously,
你说什么我一点都没看懂
did not understand a word you just said.
去走廊
ln the hall.
好
Okay.
你想要跟乔伊瞎搞
You wanna fool around with Joey?
是啊
Yeah.
自从我做过那个梦之后
Ever since l had that dream about him,
我就一直忘不了
l can't get it out of my head.
我是说那又会怎样
l mean, what's the big deal?
很多人都是那样做的
People do it all the time.
谁们  你认识谁们是朋友还瞎搞的
Who? Who do you know that are friends that just fool around?
好的  随便想想...
Okay. Off the top of my head....
唐跟珍妮特
Don and Janet.
他们是谁
Who are they?
工作上认识的人
l know them from work.
两个都是吗
Both of them?
不  只有其中一个
No, just one of them.
哪一个
Which one?
我不知道
l don't know.
我刚才说了哪些名字呢
What were the names l just said?
不行  瑞秋
No, Rachel,
事情会变得很复杂的
things could get incredibly complicated.
好吧  你说的对
All right. You're right.
我不会对乔伊怎样的
l won't do anything with Joey.
我只是以为…
l just thought it--
好的  那就两杯的龙蒿
Okay, so that's two cups of tarragon,
一磅的苏打粉  还有一个红洋葱
one pound of baking soda and a red onion?
你是想要煮什么呢
What the hell are you cooking?
《老友记》  第九季 第20集 肥皂剧演员大派对
Friends S09E20 The One With The Soap Opera Party
你们不会相信
You guys won't believe
我今天要做什么样的工作
what l have to do for work today.
但是罗斯
Yes, but, Ross,
是你自己选择
you chose a career
要谈论恐龙的工作的
of talking about dinosaurs.
有两个教授
There are these two professors
要加入我的部门
who are joining my department...
而我要在这里跟他们碰面
...and l have to meet them here
然后带他们到校园看看
and show them around campus.
那怎么会糟糕呢
What's so bad about that?
我就知道他们
l just know they'll be
肯定都是空话连篇
a couple of old windbags...
穿着在手肘的地方
...wearing tweed jackets
缝上仿麂皮的花呢外套
with suede elbow patches.
罗斯
Ross?
怎样  这些不是仿麂皮
What? These aren't suede.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我在找人
l'm looking for someone.
你认不认识
You don't, by any chance,
一个叫做罗斯·盖勒的
know a Ross Geller?
不认识
No.
嗨  我是罗斯·盖勒
Hi. Hi, l'm Ross Geller.
嗨  我是魏勒教授
Oh, hi. l'm Professor Wheeler.
喔  这...这太好了
Oh, that's-- That's-- That's nice.
很高兴见到你
lt's good to meet you.
谢谢你愿意
Thank you so much for
花时间领我转转
taking the time to show me around.
不  这一点也不麻烦的
No, it's no big deal.
如果我没有这样做
lf l weren't doing this,
反正我也只是
l'd just, you know,
在健身房健身而已
be at the gym working out.
他会介绍我们吗
ls he gonna introduce us?
我想他现在根本就看不到我们
l think we're just blurry shapes to him now.
对了  我真的很喜欢你写的…
By the way, l really enjoyed your paper...
地域隔绝与快速突变之关系的论文
...on the connection between geographic isolation and rapid mutagenesis.
我一个晚上就写完了
l wrote that in one night.
我赌二十块钱
Twenty bucks says
他们一个月内就会结婚
they're married within the month.
我们应该出发了
Well, we should probably get going.
我们有很多地方要去
You know, we've got a lot of ground to cover.
不是有另外一位教授
lsn't another professor
要加入我们吗
supposed to come with us?
我想应该没有
l don't think so.
我非常确定
l'm pretty sure.
是从康乃尔大学来的史伯夫教授
A Professor Spafford from Cornell?
他可能是迟到了
Well, he's obviously late,
而我上课的规矩就是
and the rule in my class is:
如果你不能准时到
lf you can't come on time,
那就干脆不要到
then don't come at all.
我很多学生都选择了这样做
An option that many of my students use.
我们要走了吗
Shall we?
我们不用等他吗
We shouldn't wait for him?
你知道吗  他是个大男孩了
You know what, he's a big boy.
我确定他可以找到我们的  好吗
l'm sure he'll find us, okay?
盖勒教授吗
Professor Geller?
喔  妈的
Oh, damn it!
嗨  乔伊  我是珍·罗杰斯
Hi, Joey, it's Jan Rogers.
等不及要参加你今晚的派对了
Can't wait for your party tonight.
我忘记你的地址了
Listen, l forgot your address.
可以回电给我吗   谢谢  拜
Can you give me a call? Thanks. Bye.
怎么了
What's happenin'?
真可惜你没有办法参加
lt's a real shame you can't make it
今晚的女人独角戏
to that one-woman show tonight.
我也想去
l'd love to,
但是我隔天要好早起来
but l gotta get up so early the next day.
你知道我的  工作最重要
You know me, work comes first.
是啊  是啊
Oh, yeah, yeah.
嗨  乔伊  我是珍·罗杰斯
Hi, Joey, it's Jan Rogers.
等不及参加你今晚的派对了
Can't wait for your party tonight.
白痴珍·罗杰斯
Stupid Jan Rogers!
你今晚要开派对
You are having a party tonight?
我跟《我们的日子》的人员
l'm kind of having a thing for
办了一个聚会
the Days of Our Lives people.
而你却不告诉我们
And you weren't gonna tell us?
你认为你可以逃得掉吗
How did you think you were gonna get away with that?
我每年都这样做啊
l do it every year.
你每年都这样做
You do that every year?!
我不需要告诉你的
l didn't have to tell you that!
天啊  我比珍·罗杰斯还愚蠢
God, l'm stupider than Jan Rogers!
你为什么不邀请我们参加你的派对呢
Why wouldn't you invite us to your parties?
你还好
You're fine, okay?
但是其他人在名人面前
But everyone else acts
都表现的像傻瓜一样
like an idiot around famous people.
那么  就只邀请我就好了啊
Well, then, so just invite me.
拜托  我只是想对你和蔼点
Please, l was trying to be nice.
你是最糟糕的
You're the worst one.
乔伊  别这样  拜托啦
Joey, come on! Please, please?
让我参加  我会克制自己  我保证
Let me come. l will behave. l promise.
我会克制自己  拜托
l will behave. Please, please, please.
好啦  你可以参加
Okay, fine. You can come.
但是不要告诉其他人
But don't tell anybody else.
八点钟在楼顶上面
lt's up on the roof at 8.
肥皂剧演员楼顶派对
A soap-opera roof party?!
我要参加肥皂剧演员楼顶派对
l'm going to a soap-opera roof party!
喔  我的天啊
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
好了  发泄完了
And it's out of my system.
然后我老婆跟我搭游轮到加拉巴哥（厄瓜多尔的一个省  位于太平洋东部）
And then my wife and l went on a cruise to the Galbagos.
你们不会相信他们的
There was a seafood buffet
海鲜自助餐厅有多棒
you wouldn't believe.
有蛤蜊  河蚌还有生蚝...
There were clams and mussels and oysters...
还有螃蟹...
...and cracked crab...
还有花蟹...
...and snow crab...
还有帝王蟹
...and king crab.
真可惜我对带壳类海鲜对敏
lt's a pity l'm allergic to shellfish.
你大学是在哪念的呢
So where did you get your undergraduate degree?
而且我不只对那些过敏
And that's not all l'm allergic to.
喔  还没有结束啊
Oh, it's not over.
我还有对花生跟腰果过敏
l'm also allergic to peanuts and cashews...
还有杏仁果跟榛果...
...and almonds and filberts--
所以基本上是所有的坚果类
So basically all nuts!
有趣的是  并不尽然
lnterestingly, no.
你在处理"有趣的"这个词的时候
Kinda playing fast and loose with
太轻率了
the word "interesting"
不好意思失陪一下
lf you'll excuse me,
我要去洗手间
l'm going to use the restroom.
喔  我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我已经丧失活下去的意志力了
l've lost the will to live.
我们甩了他
Let's ditch him.
什么
What?
在他还在洗手间的时候
While he's still in the bathroom.
我求求你
l am begging you.
好的
Okay. Okay, fine,
但是我有个问题要先问你
but l just have one question for you.
我们出去的时候
When we exit,
应该是用走的  跑的...
should we walk or run...
跳的还是散步...
...or prance or stroll--?
别说了
Stop it! Stop it!
他的话说得慢  搞不好尿得快
He talks slow, but he might pee fast.
我们快走
Okay, let's move!
你们好  这位是查莉
Oh, hey, you guys, this is Charlie.
查莉  这是菲比
Charlie, this is Phoebe
还有我妹妹莫妮卡
and my sister, Monica.
嗨
Hi.
查莉将要加入我们系上
Charlie will be joining my department.
你也是古生物学家吗
You're a paleontologist too?
是的
Yeah.
那好  你对于...
Oh, okay. Now, what do you think...
雷诺的分割节肢动物
...of Renyard's new theory of
多样性的新理论有何评价
species variegation in segmented arthropods?
我觉得他有点过时了
Well, l think he's a little out there,
但是他是有些有趣的观点
but he does have some interesting ideas.
很抱歉  我要接一下电话
Oh, l'm sorry. l have to take this.
不好意思
Excuse me.
雷诺的物种多样性
Renyard's theory of species variegation?
我在你的咖啡桌上看到一篇文章
l saw the article on your coffee table.
我背下了标题想要来吓你
l memorized the title to freak you out.
你们俩个相处得愉快吗
So did you two have fun?
天啊  她真的是太棒了
Oh, my God. She's great.
我们有许多共同点
We have so much in common,
她真是太酷了  还很风趣
and she's just cool, you know? And funny.
而且我不知道你有没有注意到
And l don't know if you've noticed,
但是她真辣
but she's a hottie!
嗨
Hi!
嗨  大家听着
Hi, you guys. Listen, you know what,
我觉得不太舒服...
l'm not feeling really well...
我想我可能不能去看舞台剧表演了
...and l don't think l'm gonna get to go to the play.
真的吗  怎么了
Really? What's wrong?
我不知道  好像蛮严重的
l don't know. l think it's kind of serious.
我今天早上在电视上有看到...
You know, l was watching this thing on TV this morning...
什么关于"新堡疾病"的
...about Newcastle disease,
我想我可能感染到了
and l think l might have it.
"新堡疾病"是
Newcastle disease is
通过分泌物传染的病毒
a secretion-borne virus...
只有鸡或是其它家禽才会被传染到
...that only affects chickens and other poultry.
好的  这是谁呢
Okay, who's this?
抱歉  瑞秋
l'm sorry. Rachel,
这位是查莉·魏勒  她是我同事
this is Charlie Wheeler. She's a colleague.
嗨  我应该要跟你握手的...
Hi. Well, l would shake your hand...
但是我想你不会想要
...but l'm sure you don't want to
被传染到我的鸡病
get my chicken disease.
瑞秋  我可以跟你谈一下吗
Rachel, can l see you for a second?
当然
Sure.
你没有生病
You're not sick.
什么  我当然有
What? Yes, l am!
那么为什么你要盛装打扮
Okay, then why are you all dressed up?
当你生病的时候  你会做任何事情
When you're sick, you do whatever you can
来让自己觉得好过一些
to make yourself feel better.
你只是想要待在家里
You just want to stay home
对乔伊采取行动
so you can make a move on Joey.
不是  我听进去了你之前说的话
No, l heard you before.
事情不是这样的
That is so not what this is.
好的  那是怎么回事呢
Okay, then what is this?
好的
Okay.
乔伊跟《我们的日子》的人
Joey is having a secret
在楼顶举行秘密派对
Days of Our Lives party up on the roof.
他送你们去看舞台剧
And he sent you guys to
来甩掉你们
the play to get rid of you.
什么
What?!
什么  这是怎么回事
What? What's going on?
乔伊跟《我们的日子》的人
Joey is having a secret
在楼顶举行秘密派对
Days of Our Lives party up on the roof!
他不想要让你们知道
He didn't want you to know about it,
但是我还是过来告诉你们了
but l came over here to tell you.
你是过来说你生病的
You came to say you were sick.
你到底是教授还是侦探
All right, professor or detective?
等等  乔伊要开派对
Wait, Joey's having a party,
但不邀请我们
and he wasn't gonna invite us?
他每年都那样做的
He does it every year.
这就是为什么他要请我们去看舞台剧
That's why he's sending you to the play.
这就是为什么他请我们去中古世纪餐厅
That's why he sent us to that medieval restaurant
还有钮扣工厂
and to that button factory.
而有那次糟糕的博物馆之旅吗
And that horrible museum tour?
不是  那是我安排的
No, l arranged that.
你们好  我要上床睡觉了
Hey, you guys, l'm turning in.
祝你们玩的愉快
Have fun.
我们知道你的派对了  乔伊
We know about your party, Joey.
什么派对
What party?
游戏结束了  把睡袍脱掉吧
The game's over. Take off your robe.
好的  我是说...
Okay, l mean....
穿起来  穿起来
Close it up! Close it up!
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
嘿  你来了  太好了
Hey, you made it! All right!
很高兴你来了  谢谢你参加
Glad you could make it. Thanks for coming.
我的天啊  凯尔·罗德
Oh, my God. Kyle Lowder!
嗨
Hi.
我爱你
l love you!
喂  这就是我为什么不想邀请你
Hey. That's why l didn't invite you.
你要冷静点  好吗
You have to calm down, all right?
去喝点酒什么的
Just go get yourself a drink or something.
是啊  你是想让我这样么
Oh, yeah, that's what you want.
自制力溃堤
My inhibitions lowered.
我的天啊  你敢相信我们
Oh, my God, can you believe
被这些人包围着吗
we're surrounded by all this?
我几乎控制不了自己
l can barely control myself.
莫妮卡
Monica,
你该知道你已经结婚了
you might want to remember that you're married.
钱德勒呢
Where is Chandler anyway?
我的天啊  钱德勒
Oh, my God! Chandler!
大家都死哪去了
Where the hell is everybody?
《你为什么不喜欢我》
Why Don't You Like Me?
第一章  我的月经初潮
Chapter 1 : My First Period.
乔伊说不能要签名的
Hey, Joey said no autographs.
但是如果她有  那我也要
But if she's getting one, l want one too!
"致莫妮卡"
''To Monica.''
而且别写什么 "祝福"之类的
And none of this ''best wishes'' crap.
要写"爱"
l want ''love.''
事实上  莫妮卡
Okay, actually, Mon,
马修只是给我他的电话
Matthew was giving me his phone number.
天啊  如果我知道
Oh, man! lf l had known
我要参加这个派对…
l was coming to this party...
我就一定不会结婚
...l never would've gotten married!
很高兴认识你  瑞秋
lt was nice to meet you. Rachel.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
打电话给我
Call me.
我们会的
We will!
瞧瞧你周旋在众多男生之间
Look at you with all the guys!
我猜你把乔伊都忘光了
l guess you've forgotten all about Joey.
是的  我想我是忘了乔伊
Yeah, well, l guess l have forgotten about Joey.
而很明显地
And clearly,
你也忘了钱德勒
you've forgotten about Chandler.
拜托  钱德勒是我的挚爱
Please. Chandler's the love of my life.
皮裤耶  饶了我吧
Oh, leather pants! Have mercy!
离开波士顿对你而言
So it's probably gonna be hard for you
一定很困难吧
to leave Boston, huh?
事实上我很高兴离开那
Actually, l'm kind of happy to be leaving.
我刚刚与人分手
l just broke up with someone.
真令人伤心
Oh, so sad.
但是离开哈佛
Still, it can't be easy
一定也是不容易
for you to leave Harvard.
尤其是跟诺贝尔得主
Especially after working with
亚伯特·温麦尔共事过
a Nobel Prize winner like Albert Wintermeyer.
事实上  阿亚就是我分手的人
Actually, Albie is the guy l broke up with.
你跟亚伯特·温麦尔交往过
You dated Albert Wintermeyer?
是的
Yeah.
而你叫他"阿亚"
And you called him "Albie"?
我是说  这就像是叫亚伯特·爱因斯坦…
l mean, that's like calling Albert Einstein....
"阿亚"一样
Albie.
对  他是个很聪明的男人
Yeah, well, he is a brilliant man.
你认为吗  我是说  你跟一个...
You think? l mean, you went out with the guy...
让放射性碳测年法的精度
...who improved the accuracy of radiocarbon dating
提高十倍的男人交往
by a factor of 10!
是的  而那正是每个人
Yes, and while that is everything
对男朋友的需求
one looks for in a boyfriend...
他有很多问题
...he had a lot of issues.
像是什么呢
Oh, like what?
很抱歉  我不是要刺探隐私
l'm sorry. l don't mean to pry.
只是跟…
lt's just that this must be...
一般人看《接近好莱坞》 有一样的反应
...what regular people experience when they watch Access Hollywood.
好的  你想要知道内幕吗
Okay, you want the dirt?
阿亚非常没安全感
Albie was seriously insecure.
他对我之前男朋友
He was really intimidated
感到非常的不安
by the guy l dated before him.
谁能够威胁到
Who's intimidating to a guy
诺贝尔奖得主呢
who won the Nobel Prize?
得过两个诺贝尔奖的人
A guy who won two.
两个  什么
Two? What--?
别告诉我你跟本杰明·哈伯特交往过
Don't tell me you dated Benjamin Hobart?
是的  交往了三年
Yeah, for three years.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你有没有跟没得过
Have you ever been in a relationship
诺贝尔奖的人交往过呢
with someone who hasn't won the Nobel Prize?
没有
No.
但我的第一个男朋友比利没有
But there was my first boyfriend, Billy.
是吗  他没有得诺贝尔吗
Oh, yeah? No Nobel Prizes for him?
没有  但是他倒是得过
No, but he did just win
麦克阿瑟的 "天才奖学金"
the MacArthur ''genius grant.''
真是个窝囊废
What a loser.
要再喝点酒吗
Some more wine?
罗斯  跟查莉进行的如何呢
Hey, Ross. How's it going with Charlie?
很好  在我喝完酒之后...
Oh, great. After l finish my wine...
我平庸的头脑会爆炸
...l'm gonna blow my average-sized brains out.
怎么了
What's the matter?
她只跟天才
She only dates geniuses
还有诺贝尔奖得主交往
and Nobel Prize winners.
我的天啊
Oh, my God,
今天稍早在中国餐厅…
at the Chinese restaurant earlier today...
我把筷子放在嘴中
...l put chopsticks in my mouth
假装是长毛象
and pretended to be a woolly mammoth.
我很喜欢那样耶
l always loved that.
当然你会喜欢
Of course you would!
你的大脑比我的小
Your brains are smaller than mine!
我不能跟她交往过的男人相比
l can't compete with the guys she goes out with.
他们比我好太多了
They're so out of my league.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
还有更糟的吗
Worse?
比那还糟
Oh, much, much worse.
我还模仿琼·瑞薇演出最早的两栖人
l did my impression of Joan Rivers as one of the earliest amphibians.
"我们可以去散步吗"
''Can we walk?''
你喜欢吗
Oh, you like that?
不
No.
怎样
What?
别这样  我觉得这样很好笑啊
Come on! l think that's funny!
长毛象
Woolly mammoth.
很好笑耶
lt's good!
我想你们一定在想现在
l bet you're thinking that now would be a great time
该中场休息了 是吗
for an intermission, huh?
是的  上帝  拜托
Oh, yes. God, yes.
你们不会休息的
Well, you're not gonna get one!
因为现实生活
Because in life,
是没有中场休息的
there are no intermissions, people!
现在开始第七章
Now, Chapter 7:
说离婚等同于骂街
Divorce is a Four-Letter Word!
他怎么可以离开我呢
How could he leave me?!
我不知道  你看起来挺可爱的
l don't know. You seem lovely.
罗斯  这是我同事登克
Ross, this is one of my costars, Dirk.
登克  这是我好朋友罗斯
Dirk, this is my good friend Ross.
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
你是哪出戏的呢
So, what show are you on?
我不是演员
l'm not an actor.
我是古生物学教授
l'm a professor of paleontology.
科学什么的
That's science.
嘿  听着
Hey, well, listen,
我在 《我们的日子》里面演的是科学家
l play a scientist on Days.
我的角色刚刚赢得诺贝尔奖
Yeah, my character just won a Nobel Prize.
罗斯  登克想问你带来的那个女生
Ross, Dirk was wondering about the woman
是不是你的女朋友
you brought and if you guys are together?
嗯  不是  不过...
Well, no, but....
她只跟非常聪明的男生交往
l mean, she only goes out with really, really smart guys.
嘿  我大学入学考试考了六百九十分
Hey, l got a 690 on my SATs.
真是高分啊
l'd lead with that.
好了  就签在胸罩上面就可以了
That's it. Just sign right on the bra.
莫妮卡
Monica!
别担心乔伊  我明年不会来了
Don't worry, Joe. l won't come next year!
是怎样
What the--?
你那是什么呢
What do you got there?
只是一些男生给我的电话
Just some boys gave me their phone numbers.
真的吗  让我看看
Oh, really? Let me see.
该死  还真多男生呢
Damn, that's a lot of guys.
你不觉得自己有点骚呢
Are you a little slutty?
没错
l think l am.
让我看看有哪些小丑是够格的
Let me see if l approve of any of these clowns.
这个男的戴假发
This guy wears a rug.
喔…
Well....
这人是加拿大的
This guy's Canadian.
这个男的参加秘密教派
Oh, and this guy is in a cult, okay?
你得花五千块才能升到第三级
lt'll cost you $5000 to get to level three,
但我也没有感到有什么不同
and l don't feel any different.
跳过  哈…喔  跳过  跳过
Pass. Pa-- Oh, pass. Pass.
为什么  这些男生有什么不好的
Why? What's wrong with these guys?
嗯  没有什么特别不好的
Well, nothing major.
只是他们全都配不上你
lt's just that, you know, they're not really good enough for you...
而你应该跟最好的人在一起
...and you deserve the best.
乔伊  你真是贴心
Joey, you're so sweet.
真的  不过没关系
lt's true, but it doesn't matter.
我已经知道你会跟谁回家了
l already know who you're going home with.
谁
Who?
我
Me.
什么
What?
真的
Really?
是啊  因为我们住在一起
Yeah, because we live together.
开玩笑的  开玩笑的
lt's a joke! lt's a joke.
是啊  真好笑  我听懂了
Right! That's funny! l get it!
唬到你了
Got you!
你真好笑  乔伊
You're funny, Joey.
喔  我的天
Oh, my God.
喜欢那场舞台剧表演吗
So how did you enjoy the play?
我的天  亲爱的  我真是抱歉
Oh, my God. Honey, l am so, so, so, so sorry.
没错
Well, you should be.
你错失了戏剧史上
You missed the most powerful three hours
最强劲的三个小时
in the history of the theater.
你真的喜欢吗
You really liked it?
对  一开始我是很讨厌的
Oh, yeah. l mean, at first l hated it.
我一定会的啊
But why wouldn't l?
因为身为男人
Because as a man,
我就是被训练成不要聆听的
l've been trained not to listen!
但是在第十六章之后
But after Chapter 16:
《肥胖  单身而且准备好交往》
Fat, Single and Ready to Mingle...
我就被鼓舞起来了
...l was uplifted.
真的吗
Oh, really?
是的
Oh, yeah.
我根本不晓得
l had no idea the amazing journey
女人的经历过程是这样的神奇
you go through as a woman.
告诉我...
Tell me--
跟我说说你的月经初潮
Tell me about your first period.
不
No!
有人在你的胸罩上签名吗
Did somebody sign your bra?
我是十三岁时候来的  非常难过
So l got it when l was 13. Very difficult.
罗斯  听着
Hey, Ross? So listen,
关于你跟那个恐龙女生的事
about you and the dinosaur girl?
你真的就要让几个诺贝尔奖
Are you really just gonna
把你吓走吗
let a couple of Nobel Prizes scare you off?
那是什么啊  不过是张纸吗
What is that? Come on, a piece of paper?
事实上是一百万的奖金
lt's actually a million-dollar prize.
查莉你真行
Go, Charlie!
但是我的重点是...
But my point is...
她是跟他们交往过
...okay, so she dated them,
不过都分手了啊
but she also broke up with them.
或许她正在寻找
Maybe she's looking to, you know,
一般平凡的博士而已
slum it with some average Joe Ph.D.
或许吧
Yeah, maybe,
而我的事业正在发展中
and l do have my whole career in front of me.
我是说...
l mean....
我还是有可能赢得诺贝尔奖的
l could still win a Nobel Prize.
虽然我上两份论文
Although the last two papers l've written
被广泛地批评过
were widely discredited.
你不只是聪明而已
You're so much more than just brains.
你很贴心  很善良又很风趣
You are sweet and kind and funny.
还有性感
And sexy.
好的  给她一个机会见识这全部
Okay, well, give her a chance to see all that.
对  你说的没错
Yeah. Yeah. You're right.
谢谢  我要去找她了
Thanks. l'm gonna go find her.
太好了
Good for you.
还有你关于泥盆纪时期突显均势的论文
And your paper on punctuated equilibrium
是有很精辟见解的
in the Devonian Era was topnotch.
不要再翻我的东西了
Stop going through my stuff!
我只想让你知道
l just wanted to let you know
我改变主意了
l've changed my mind.
我要做了
l'm gonna do it.
我要去亲乔伊
l'm gonna kiss Joey.
不  你不行
No! You can't!
朋友在一起是件坏事
Friends hooking up is a bad idea.
拜托  那你跟钱德勒呢
Please! What about you and Chandler?
那是不一样的  我喝醉了而且犯了傻
That's different. l was drunk and stupid.
我也醉了啊
Well, hello?
那些给你电话的男生呢
What about all the guys that you got the phone numbers from?
你为什么不去亲其中一个
Why don't you just kiss one of them.
我是可以…
l could...
但是我不想  我想要亲乔伊
...but l don't want to. l want to kiss Joey.
好吧  我认为这样是不对的
All right. l think it's a big mistake,
但那是你自己的决定
but it's your decision.
我要去做了
l'm gonna do it.
而我无法阻止你吗
And l can't stop you?
对
No.
那至少把那些电话号码给我吧
Well, can l at least have the phone numbers.
瑞秋
Hey, Rach,
你有看到查莉吗
have you seen Charlie anywhere?
我总比他聪明多了吧
l'm smarter than him!
谢谢你送我们票  钱德勒
Hey, thank you so much for these tickets, Chandler.
这对我是很重要的经历
This was a really important experience for me
而我想跟你们分享
and l wanted to share it with you.
你真是太好了
You're so wonderful.
《你为什么不喜欢我》
Why Don't You Like Me?
第一章  我的月经初潮
Chapter 1 : My First Period.
我不敢相信你们竟然这么好骗
l can't believe you guys bought that.
慢慢享受死刑吧
Enjoy your slow death.